Finding Aid for the Norman Maurer Papers PASC.0086
UCLA Library Special Collections
Norman Maurer papers
1976-1983
UCLA Library Special Collections
Maurer, Norman
Maurer, Joan Howard
PASC.0086
18.0 Linear Feet (43 boxes)
Norman Mauer was writer, film director and producer, and also worked for many years in television animation for Hanna Barbera and ABC, writing and editing. The collection consists of scripts, photocopies of storyboards, and outlines for children's animated television programs including, The Adventures of Goldie Gold (1981), Dingbat and the creeps (1980), Fangface (1979), Heathcliff (1979-81), Marmaduke (1981), Mork and Mindy (1980-82), Plastic family (1980-81), Richie Rich (1979-81), Scooby and Scrappy Doo (1980-81), Super friends (1980-81), and Thundarr the barbarian (1979-81).
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Norman and Joan Maurer 1981, 1982, 1985, and 1987.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9922213503606533
Biography
Norman Maurer was born circa 1926. He started his career as cartoonist for Lev Gleason Publications. He illustrated Daredevil comics, and Boy comics, among others and wrote comic books including three series of Three Stooges comics and ghost writing on Dennis the menace comic books; Maurer also co-created the first 3-D comics. He joined Columbia Pictures in 1956 and produced films including The Three stooges meet Hercules and Who's minding the mint. He wrote stories for four of Columbia's Three Stooges features and produced and directed several Stooges television pilots. In 1975 Maurer joined Hanna-Barbera as writer and story editor; he worked as consultant for animated cartoon series at CBS from 1978 to 1979 and NBC in 1980. Maurer died November 23, 1986 in Los Angeles, CA.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of materials related to the career of writer Norman Maurer. Includes scripts, photocopies of storyboards, and outlines for children's animated television programs including, The Adventures of Goldie Gold (1981), Dingbat and the creeps (1980), Fangface (1979), Heathcliff (1979-81), Marmaduke (1981), Mork and Mindy (1980-82), Plastic family (1980-81), Richie Rich (1979-81), Scooby and Scrappy Doo (1980-81), Super friends (1980-81), and Thundarr the barbarian (1979-81). Many programs were produced by Ruby Spears Productions or Hanna-Barbera Productions. Also includes a small amount of material related to the career of writer Joan Howard Maurer.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by program titles.
Television writers -- United States -- Archives.; Animated television programs -- United States -- Archives.; Maurer, Norman
- Artwork
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 8/20/1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    General note
    CURSE OF THE SNAKE PEOPLE.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 7/21/1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    INSERT.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 8/20/1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 6/24/1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    ISLAND OF TERRORS - ACT I.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 7/27/1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    MAIN TITLES.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 5/27/1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    NIGHT OF THE CRYSTAL SKULL - FINAL BOARD.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 8/12/1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    NIGHT OF THE WALKING DOOM.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 7/24/1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    PIRATE OF THE AIRWAYS!
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 7/13/1981 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    PROPHET OF DOOM.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 7/15/1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    RACE AGAINST TIME - ACT I.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 6/12/1981 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    RED DUST OF DOOM - ACT I.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 6/22/1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    REVENGE OF THE ANCIENT ASTRONAUT - ACT I.
  - BABY HUEY, 12/5/1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    GOOD SCOUT HUEY! - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - BABY HUEY, 11/21/1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    WOLF FOR HIRE - REVISED VERSION.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 9, Folder 14)
    BATTY BOO-TICIANS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 9, Folder 15)
    BEACH BLANKET BOZOS - FINAL BOARD.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 5/1/1980 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    BUNGLING BABYSITTERS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 9, Folder 16)
    CARNIVAL CUT-UPS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 9, Folder 17)
    CREEP CROP CRACK-UPS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 5/1/1980 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    DETECTIVE DING-A-LINGS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 9, Folder 18)
    DOOR TO DOOR SALESCREEPS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 9, Folder 19)
    FOOTBALL FLUNKIES.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 35, Folder 12)
    HEALTH NUTS - FIRST DRAFT.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 9, Folder 20)
    HEIR TODAY, GONE TOMORROW.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 9, Folder 21)
    HIGH FLYING FOOLS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 9, Folder 22)
    IT'S SNOW JOB FOR A CREEP - FINAL BOARD.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 10, Folder 1)
    LE-MANSTER RALLY.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 10, Folder 2)
    LUMBERING LOONEYS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 10, Folder 3)
    NAUTICAL NOOD-NICKS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 10, Folder 4)
    NO NEWS IS GHOUL NEWS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 7/8/1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    NUTTY KNIGHTS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 5/20/1980 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    PRIZED POOCH - FINAL BOARD.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 10, Folder 6)
    RETAIL RUCKUS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 10, Folder 7)
    SAFARI SAPS - FINAL BOARD.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 4/14/1980 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    SERVICE STATION SCREWBALLS - FIRST DRAFT.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 10, Folder 8)
    SHOWBIZ SHENANIGANS - FINAL BOARD.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 4/22/1980 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    TREASURE HAUNT.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 10, Folder 9)
    U.F.OAFS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS (Box 10, Folder 10)
    WINDOW WASHOUTS.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 8/7/1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    ALL THIS AND TIMBUKTU! - ACTS I & II.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 10, Folder 12)
    ARABIAN KNIGHTS - ACT I AND INSERTS.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 7/29/1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    AROUND THE WORLD IN EIGHTY WAYS - ACT I.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 6/15/1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    DOUBLE JEOPARDY - ACTS I & II.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 6/24/1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    FJORDS AND SORCERY -ACTS I & II.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 11, Folder 1)
    GONE WITH THE WAND - ACT I.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 11, Folder 2)
    IT'S A JUNGLE OUT THERE!.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 5/28/1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    IT'S ALL DOWNHILL FROM HERE - ACT I.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 5/11/1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    KELP! - ACT I.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 11, Folder 5)
    KING FOR A DAY - ACT I.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 7/2/1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    MAIN TITLES - REVISED VERSION.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 11, Folder 6)
    MAY THE FARCE BE WITH YOU - ACT I AND INSERTS.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 11, Folder 7)
    MING FU TO YOU TOO! - ACT I.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 7/17/1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    PERILOUS PAULINE - ACT I.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 11, Folder 9)
    SCIENCE FRICTION - ACT I.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 7/15/1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    THERE'S NO PLACE LIKE ROME - ACTS I & II.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 5/15/1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    TIME SCHLEP - ACTS I & II.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 12, Folder 3)
    TWENTY-THOUSAND DRACHMA PYRAMID (THE) - ACT I.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 12, Folder 4)
    VAMPIRE STRIKES BACK (THE) - ACT I.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 12, Folder 5)
    WESTWARD WHOA! - ACT I.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG (Box 12, Folder 6)
    YOU'LL NEVER GET WITCH - ACT I.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 4/9/1980 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    ANGLING ANGLER.
  - HEATHCLIFF (Box 14, Folder 5)
    BIG FISH STORY (THE).
  - HEATHCLIFF, 6/8/1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    BRIEF CASE OF CLOAK AND DAGGAR (A).
  - HEATHCLIFF, 2/14/1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    CAKE FLAKES.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 3/5/1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    CAT AND THE BEANSTALK.
  - HEATHCLIFF (Box 14, Folder 9)
    CAT KIT (THE).
  - HEATHCLIFF, 4/13/1981 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    CAUGHT CAT NAPPING.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 5/8/1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    CLON'EN AROUND!.
  - HEATHCLIFF (Box 14, Folder 12)
    CLOSE ENCOUNTER (A).
  - HEATHCLIFF, 5/18/1981 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    CRAZY DAZE.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 4/6/1981 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    DUD BOAT (THE).
  - HEATHCLIFF, 5/22/1981 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    GATOR GO-ROUND.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 4/22/1980 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    GOLD DIGGER DAZE.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 4/16/1980 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    GREAT CHASE (THE) - REVISED.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 6/14/1980 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    GREAT COP N' CAT CHASE (THE).
  - HEATHCLIFF, 4/24/1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    GREAT MILK FACTORY FRACAS (THE).
  - HEATHCLIFF, 5/5/1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    HEATHCLIFF AND THE SLEEPING BEAUTY.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 7/25/1980 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    HEATHCLIFF OF SHERWOOD FOREST.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 6/9/1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    HEATHCLIFF PINNOCHIO (A).
  - HEATHCLIFF, 6/23/1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    HEATHCLIFF vs. THE MOUSE TRAPPER.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 1/17/1980 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    KITTY A LA CARTE.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 4/28/1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    LION AROUND THE HOUSE.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 7/7/1980 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    MASCOT RUMBLE.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 6/16/1980 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    MILK RUN MAYHEM - REVISED VERSION.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 5/13/1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    MUSH, HEATHCLIFF, MUSH!.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 4/14/1980 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    MYSTERY LOVES COMPANY.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 4/13/1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    NEW KIT ON THE BLOCK.
  - HEATHCLIFF (Box 15, Folder 15)
    NO TITLE.
  - HEATHCLIFF (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - HEATHCLIFF, 1/23/1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - HEATHCLIFF (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - HEATHCLIFF (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - HEATHCLIFF, 5/31/1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    OF MICE AND MEN.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 6/23/1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    PUMPING IRONY.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 4/1/1980 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    RED HOT RIDING HOODED HEATHCLIFF.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 5/12/1980 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    ROBINSON CRUISE HO!.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 5/20/1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    RODEO DOUGH -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 6/20/1981 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    STAR TRICK - TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 4/15/1980 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    SUGGESTED OPENING TITLES.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 5/8/1981 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    TABBY AND THE PIRATE.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 8/25/1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    WATCHCAT (THE) - REVISED VERSION.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 5/28/1980 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    ZITS.
  - HEATHCLIFF AND MARMADUKE, 7/15/1981 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    BRIDGE - 15 SECOND SHORT.
  - HEATHCLIFF AND MARMADUKE, 7/21/1981 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    BRIDGE #2.
  - HEATHCLIFF AND MARMADUKE, 7/15/1981 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    MAIN TITLES - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - HEATHCLIFF/DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 8/4/1981 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 7/8/1981 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    APRIL FOOLS IN PARIS.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 8/14/1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    BIGFOOT.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 5/1/1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    INVASION OF THE BOOBY HATCHERS (THE).
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 6/8/1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    JUNGLE JUMPERS.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 6/19/1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    NAVAL FLUFF.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 8/7/1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    WHEN THE MOON COMES OVER THE WEREWOLF! - FINAL FIXES.
  - LENNY AND SCRAWNY, 1/3/1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    LAST IN SPACE.
  - LENNY AND SCRAWNY, 1/24/1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    UNTITLED - TWO COPIES, DIFFERENT DATES.
  - MARMADUKE, 4/24/1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    BABYSITTING SHENANIGANS.
  - MARMADUKE, 6/11/1981 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    BARKING FOR DOLLARS.
  - MARMADUKE, 6/24/1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    BEACH BRAWL.
  - MARMADUKE, 6/22/1981 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    BEARLY CAMPING.
  - MARMADUKE, 8/20/1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    BONE TO PICK WITH MARMADUKE (A).
  - MARMADUKE, 5/27/1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    CAPER CRACKER (THE).
  - MARMADUKE, 8/21/1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    DOGGONE FUNNY (14) - SHORTS.
  - MARMADUKE, 6/17/1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    DOUBLE TROUBLE MAKERS.
  - MARMADUKE, 1/19/1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    FRET VET.
  - MARMADUKE, 7/6/1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    GOLD FEVER FRACAS.
  - MARMADUKE, 6/22/1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    GONE WITH THE WHIM.
  - MARMADUKE, 7/8/1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    HOME RUN ROVER.
  - MARMADUKE, 4/29/1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    KITTY SITTER (THE).
  - MARMADUKE, 7/15/1981 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    LEAPING LEPRECHAUN.
  - MARMADUKE, 7/1/1981 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    LEMONADE KID (THE).
  - MARMADUKE, 5/28/1981 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    MARMADUKE OF THE MOVIES.
  - MARMADUKE, 8/11/1981 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    MARMADUKE'S RIDDLES (8) - SCRIPT AND ANIMATION.
  - MARMADUKE, 5/21/1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    MISSY MYSTIQUE.
  - MARMADUKE, 8/4/1981 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    PLAYGROUNDED.
  - MARMADUKE, 7/1/1981 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    SCHOOL DAZE.
  - MARMADUKE, 6/2/1981 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    SEA-GOING WATCHDOG.
  - MARMADUKE, 7/17/1981 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    SHUTTLE OFF TO BUFFALO.
  - MARMADUKE, 3/2/1981 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    SUBURBAN COWBOY.
  - MARMADUKE, 6/29/1981 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    TRICKY TREAT.
  - MARMADUKE, 6/2/1981 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    WONDERMUTT.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 6/30/1982 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    BEAUTY CONTEST (THE).
  - MORK AND MINDY, 8/18/1982 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    DISAPPEARANCE (THE) -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY (Box 41, Folder 8)
    EVERY DOING HAS ITS DAY.
  - MORK AND MINDY (Box 43, Folder 12)
    FINAL BOARD FOR INSERT--UNTITLED ?.
  - MORK AND MINDY (Box 41, Folder 4)
    FLUKE SPOOK (THE).
  - MORK AND MINDY, 8/3/1982 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    INCREDIBLE SHRINKING MORK (THE) -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 8/9/1982 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    MORK FOR MAYOR - FINAL BOARD.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 8/25/1982 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    MORK WITH THE MIDAS TOUCH (THE).
  - MORK AND MINDY, 6/18/1982 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    MORK-MAN vs. ORK-MAN.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 7/26/1981 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    ON YOUR MORK, GET SET, GO! -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 6/23/1982 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    ORKAN WITHOUT A CAUSE -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 7/19/1982 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    RODEO RUBE - FINAL BOARD.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 6/3/1982 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    TO ORK OR NOT TO ORK, THAT IS THE QUESTION - FINAL BOARD.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 7/27/1982 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    TOUCHDOWN MORK -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 7/15/1982 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    VISIT (THE) -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - PITFALL HARRY (Box 31, Folder 8)
    MAIN MODELS.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 17, Folder 19)
    ABOMINABLE SNOW SPORT (THE).
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 6/16/1981 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    ALI BABA BABY.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 17, Folder 21)
    BABY PLAS' FINNY FRIEND - FINAL BOARD.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 9, Folder 3)
    BABYSITTER BLUES.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 35, Folder 4)
    BAD LUCK STROLL.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 31, Folder 17)
    BASEBALL BULLY.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 9, Folder 4)
    BIRTHDAY BLOWOUT.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 6/27/1981 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    CALAMITY CRUISE.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 9, Folder 5)
    CLUBHOUSE CALAMITY - FINAL BOARD.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 18, Folder 7)
    CRIME COSTUME CAPER (THE).
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 7/31/1981 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    DOCTOR STRANGELEAF.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 9, Folder 6)
    FROGNAPPED.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 9, Folder 7)
    HAIRCUT HEADACHE - FINAL BOARD.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 17, Folder 24)
    KEWPIE DOLL CAPER (THE).
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 6/23/1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    MIGHTY MUSEUM MESS.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 9, Folder 8)
    MOVIE MISCHIEF.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 9, Folder 9)
    MUMMY MADNESS.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 18, Folder 2)
    OZARK FAMILY FEUD.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 18, Folder 9)
    PLASTIC MAN MEETS PLASTIC APE.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 18, Folder 3)
    RODEO RUCKUS.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 18, Folder 4)
    ROYAL GARGOYLE FOIL (THE).
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 18, Folder 5)
    RUSTLIN' RASCALS.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 9, Folder 10)
    SLEEPWALKING SNAFU -TWO COPIES, ONE FINAL.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 3/21/1980 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    STROMBOMBI'S CIRCUS.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 9, Folder 11)
    TIGER TROUBLE - FINAL BOARD.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 9, Folder 12)
    TROPICAL TROUBLE.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 7/7/1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    WHO UNDO THE ZOO.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY (Box 9, Folder 13)
    WITCHING WORRIES.
  - Q-BERT (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/26/1981 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    AROUND THE WORLD ON EIGHTY CENTS.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 21, Folder 8)
    BASEBALL DOLLAR.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 18, Folder 11)
    BUTLERING MADE EASY.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/26/1981 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    BYE-BYE-BABY.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 21, Folder 9)
    CANINE CADET.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/24/1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    CARNIVAL MAN.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 18, Folder 14)
    CAVEBOY RICHIE.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 18, Folder 15)
    CHILLY DOG.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 18, Folder 16)
    CHOWHOUND.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 18, Folder 17)
    COUNTERFEIT DOLLAR.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 18, Folder 18)
    CUR-WASH.
  - RICHIE RICH, 7/6/1981 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    DAY THE ESTATE STOOD STILL! (THE).
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 18, Folder 20)
    DISASTER MASTER.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/3/1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    DOG GONE.
  - RICHIE RICH, 1/18/1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    GOING GOING GONE - HANDWRITTEN NOTES.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 19, Folder 3)
    GREAT CHARITY TRAIN ROBBERY (THE).
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/26/1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    I WANT MY MUMMY.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 19, Folder 5)
    IT'S NO GIGGLING MATTER.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/2/1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    KING BEE.
  - RICHIE RICH, 3/11/1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    KITTY SITTER.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/19/1981 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    MISCHIEF MOVIE.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 36, Folder 18)
    MODELS.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/16/1981 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    MONEY TALKS.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 19, Folder 10)
    MOST UNFORGETTABLE BUTLER (THE).
  - RICHIE RICH, 3/7/1980 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    MUSCLE BEACH - FIVE ITEMS.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/28/1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    NO SUBSTITUTE FOR A WATCH DOG.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/1/1981 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    No title.
  - RICHIE RICH, 4/8/1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    ONE OF OUR AIRCRAFT CARRIERS IS MISSING.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/8/1981 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    ORDINARY DAY (A)N.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/25/1980 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    PIGGY BANK PRANK.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 19, Folder 15)
    PRANKSTER BEWARE.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 19, Folder 16)
    RARE SCARE (THE).
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/29/1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    RICH MICE.
  - RICHIE RICH, 4/7/1980 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    RICHIE AND THE ROBOTNAPPERS.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/19/1981 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    RICHIE OF THE ROUND TABLE.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/8/1981 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    RICHIE RICH GEMS (57) - 30-SECOND SHORTS.
  - RICHIE RICH, 7/15/1981 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    ROBOT ROBBER.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 20, Folder 2)
    SCHOOLHOUSE ROMP.
  - RICHIE RICH, 3/27/1980 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    SILENCE IS GOLDEN - THREE COPIES, DIFFERENT DATES.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 20, Folder 4)
    SINISTER SPORTS SPECTACULAR (THE).
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 20, Folder 5)
    SNOWBOUNDERS (THE).
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/21/1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    SPACE SHARK - TWO COPIES, DIFFERENT DATES.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 20, Folder 7)
    SPECIAL TALENT (A).
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/8/1981 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    TOOTH IS STRANGER THAN FICTION.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 20, Folder 8)
    TV DOLLAR.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 34, Folder 11)
    VARIETY OF DIFFERENT COMIC STRIPS (32) - NOTES INCLUDED.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/19/1981 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    VILLAINS INCORPORATED.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/28/1981 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    VOODOO ISLAND.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 20, Folder 12)
    WACKY WEATHER - COLOR STORYBOARD.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 20, Folder 13)
    WATCHDOG/ASS'T. CHEF.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 20, Folder 14)
    WELCOME, UNCLE CAUTIOUS.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 20, Folder 15)
    WIPED OUT! - TWO DIFFERENT COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - RICHIE RICH/SCOOBY-DOO SHOW (THE), 7/2/1981 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    MAIN TITLES - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RIN-TIN TWINS (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO (Box 21, Folder 13)
    ALASKAN KING COWARDS.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/26/1981 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    BACKSTAGE SCOOBY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/7/1980 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    BUNGLE IN THE JUNGLE (A).
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/21/1981 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    CANINE TO FIVE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 4/16/1980 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    CHINESE FOOD FACTORY (THE) -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 3/21/1980 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    CLOSE ENCOUNTER WITH A STRANGE KIND (A) - TWO DIFFFERENT COPIES.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 8/8/1980 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    EH TO, SCOOB?.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/19/1981 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    EXCALIBUR SCOOBY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 3/25/1980 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    FIT NIGHT OUT FOR BATS (A).
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 10/10/1980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    FRIGHT AT THE OPERA (A).
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/19/1980 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    HANG IN THERE SCOOBY!.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/28/1981 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    HARD HAT SCOOBY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/28/1981 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    HOT HOUSE SCOOBY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 10/15/1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    INVASION OF THE SCOOBY SNATCHERS (THE) - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/18/1981 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    LIGHTHOUSE KEEPER SCOOBY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO (Box 22, Folder 3)
    MONLIGHT MADNESS.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/19/1980 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    MUMMY'S THE WORD.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/7/1980 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    OLD CAT AND MOUSE GAME (THE).
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 8/14/1981 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    PIGSKIN SCOOBY - TWO COPIES, DIFFERENT DATES.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/30/1981 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    PUNK ROCK SCOOBY -TWO COPIES, ONE FINAL.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/9/1981 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    RICKSHAW SCOOBY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 10/28/1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    SCOOBY AND THE BANDIT.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 9/23/1980 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    SCOOBY AT THE CENTER OF THE WORLD.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/16/1981 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    SCOOBY DOO 2000! - REVISED VERSION.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/4/1981 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    SCOOBY DOOBY GOO.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 10/20/1980 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    SCOOBY DOOBY GURU.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/12/1981 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    SCOOBY GHOSTS WEST.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO (Box 22, Folder 13)
    SCOOBY GUMBO.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/15/1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    SCOOBY IN WONDERLAND.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/26/1981 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    SCOOBY SAVES THE WORLD.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO (Box 22, Folder 15)
    SCOOBY-NOCCHIO.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/11/1980 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    SCOOBY'S BULL FRIGHT.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/5/1980 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    SCOOBY'S DESERT DILEMMA - REVISED VERSION.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/28/1981 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    SCOOBY'S ESCAPE FROM ATLANTIS.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/3/1980 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    SCOOBY'S FANTASTIC ISLAND.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/20/1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    SCOOBY'S FUN ZONE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/15/1981 (Box 23, Folder 2)